<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Welcome to Fi+</string>
    <string name="sign_up_activity">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="mainscreen_activity">What\'s happening?</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_activity">Terms Of Use</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_activity">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="forgot_pw">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="view_event">Event</string>
    <string name="configure_profile">Configure Profile</string>
    <string name="recent_activities_activity">Recent Activities</string>
    <string name="view_profile">View Profile</string>
    <string name="favourite_users">Favourite Users</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">Fi+ Privacy Policy
This privacy policy governs your use of the software application Fi+ (“Application”) for mobile devices that was created by Fi+. The Application is equipped with an user interface and functionalities aiding the user to host and join fitness events.
Fi+ Privacy Policy was created with the following guidelines:
http://www.iubenda.com/blog/2013/06/10/the-need-for-privacy-policies-in-mobile-apps-an-overview/
And modified based on the following templates:
http://www.docracy.com/mobileprivacy/

What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?
User Provided Information
Registration with us is mandatory in order to be able to use the basic features of the Application.
When you register with us and use the Application, you generally provide (a) your email address, user name, password and other registration information; (b) transaction-related information, such as when you make events, respond to any events, or download or use applications from us; (c) information you provide us when you contact us for help; (d) information you enter into our system when using the Application, such as age, photos, and contact information.
By using the Application you consent to providing the above information. We may also use the information you provided us to contact your from time to time to provide you with important information, required notices, and marketing promotions.
Automatically Collected Information
In addition, the Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, your mobile device’s unique device ID, geo-targeting (e.g, zip code or city), the IP address of your mobile device, and information about the way you use the Application.
Does the Application collect precise real time location information of the device?
When you visit the mobile application, we may use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location in order to determine the city you are located within and display a list of relevant events or update your location information. We will share your location with other users or partners for the purposes of fulfilling the Application’s event matchmaking functionality and advertising.
If you do not want us to use your real time location for the purposes set forth above, you should turn off the location services for the mobile application located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the mobile application.
Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?
Yes. We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.
We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:
as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;
when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;
with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.
if Fi+ is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information.
Automatic Data Collection and Advertising
We may work with analytics companies to help us understand how the Application is being used, such as the frequency and duration of usage. We may work with advertisers and third party advertising networks to keep the cost of our Application low for users. This may involve and is not limited to the collection of Application usage, mobile device ID, and advertising statistics.
If you’d like to opt-out from third party use of this type of information to help serve targeted advertising, please visit the section entitled “Opt-out” below.
What are my opt-out rights?
You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily by uninstalling the Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network.
Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information
We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain Automatically Collected information for as long as needed for development and thereafter may store it in aggregate. If you’d like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at social.fi.er@gmail.com and we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the Application to function properly.
Children
We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at social.fi.er@gmail.com. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.
Security
We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide electronic and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. Please be aware that, although we endeavor provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.
Changes
This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy via email. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes.
Your Consent
By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing,” means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the North America. If you reside outside of North America your information will be transferred, processed and stored there under North American privacy standards.

Contact us
If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at social.fi.er@gmail.com.</string>

    <string name="terms_of_use">Fi+ Terms of Use
Fi+ Terms of Use is modified based on the following template:
http://www.bennadel.com/coldfusion/privacy-policy-generator.htm#primary-navigation
1. Terms
By accessing this mobile application, you are agreeing to be bound by these Fi+ Terms of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this application. The materials contained in this mobile application are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.
2. Use License
Permission is granted to download the materials (software) for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:
modify or copy the materials;
use the materials for any commercial purpose
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Fi+\'s mobile application;
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Fi+ at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
3. Disclaimer
The materials on Fi+\'s mobile application are provided "as is". Fi+ makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Fi+ does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its mobile application or otherwise relating to such materials or on any websites or applications linked to this application.
4. Limitations
In no event shall Fi+ or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Fi+\'s mobile application, even if Fi+ or a Fi+ authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
5. Revisions and Errata
The materials appearing on Fi+\'s mobile application could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Fi+ does not warrant that any of the materials on its mobile application are accurate, complete, or current. Fi+ may make changes to the materials contained on its mobile application at any time without notice. Fi+ does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
6. Links
Fi+ has not reviewed all of the services (websites, servers, applications) linked to its mobile application and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked service. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Fi+ of the application. Use of any such linked service is at the user\'s own risk.
7. Fi+ Terms of Use Modifications
Fi+ may revise these terms of use for its mobile application at any time without notice. By using this mobile application you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms of Use.
8. Governing Law
Any claim relating to Fi+\'s mobile application shall be governed by the laws of the Province of Alberta without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
Fi+ Terms of Use applicable to use of a the Fi+ Mobile Application.</string>


</resources>
